I need a score better outside of classic lit.
Won't be able to get a doctor's note for the quiz.
Too bad quiz allergies aren't real.
Kutatsu study party?
Exams are almost here.
Looks cozy. How's about a join you kiddos?
Go away.
Um, there actually isn't room for you.
Just Sota, Miyamura, Mom, and me. That's it.
You know, you treat me worse by the day.
I'm gonna cry.
I found this to be a genius.
Maybe later, he sa你说 it didn't be better now.
Mainly, no normals is really good.
A last strived sting, however,
But this might have gone insane.
Come, your sis is a voter.
Like you, your VAS
This is your fourth star's life.
Thank you.
I'm just calling and I would really like to answer.
Answer where you are.
I am not letting the carpet.
Whoa.
I guess I dozed off.
That's like 10.
Keep it down, Kiyoko.
I wonder if you didn't bridge my life with every move you make.
Oh, you're being ridiculous, but what else is new?
Right, Miyamoto?
Wait, what's wrong?
I need to take a leak.
Oh, but I should wake Sota first.
I get sick if he sleeps here all night.
Hey, little buddy.
Whoa!
You're twisting my leg, funny, and I got it!
Tell you, quit moving, Kiyosuke!
We created a world where we endlessly wound each other.
Should we call for help or simply pray?
Calling for help would be too embarrassing since we're all tangled up like a pose from some edgy manga.
Aren't we, Miyamoto?
It's about to break!
Kiyosuke, why are you here?
Things were fine till your stupid self joined in!
Well, excuse me.
If I could get out, I already would have.
I'm done.
My body's paralyzed by the need for a bathroom.
It's up to you guys now.
Don't you dare call it quits!
Let's assess the dilemma.
One of us must be sacrificed.
All right.
I can try and yank my way free.
Wait, time out.
Kiyosuke's right leg is currently trapped between my legs.
Hori's are also wrapped pretty tightly around me.
Pulling will only cause excruciating pain before ultimately failing.
Valid points.
Then what's the plan?
You two bite the bullet while I tear my way out of here.
Hold it, Buster!
Just what kind of anti-autic idea is that?
If someone needs to rescue more than me, speak now or forever hold your pain!
I am uncomfortable too.
My skirt flip, but you don't hear me whining, do you?
What?
How's that even an issue?
You're hidden!
Don't go back to sleep!
Oh, man.
Maybe we shouldn't have had and drunk all that tea about now.
Hey, wait.
There.
If I do that, then...
Holy stinkin' crap!
It's actually free!
It is?
That's great!
I got one out too!
Rise and shine, sleeping ugly!
Freedom is mine!
What do you think?
You make it in time?
I think I'm just glad the crisis has ended.
Just spitballing?
But instead of lying down in three different directions, let's try facing the same way.
Yeah, okay.
I woke up well after dark the last time I was here.
So I'll head home around seven today.
Which gives us about an hour.
Just enough time for a nap.
Don't even play.
Hey, aren't you Sengoku's boy?
Huh?
Remember me?
Used to come over to our house and play all the time when you were little.
Kyo-chan's dad?
Yeah, I remember.
Dang, you sure grew up!
Well, you are Kyo-ko's age, right?
Puberty at work.
Man, that's it.
Listen, Kakiru.
The horis are bad news.
Have been ever since high school.
Hold your ground or they'll lead you by the nose and that's all she wrote!
Wait, that's all who wrote?
I'm just telling you they're trouble!
So, Kat!
I mean, Takiru.
How's your old man been doing?
My name's Kakiru!
And my dad's doing well, thank you.
Yeah.
He's doing well, is he?
Something tells me he wants to change that!
Pardon me, sir, but I was on my way home from buying erasers.
Ah, stop by our place for a visit while you're in the area.
Come warm yourself up before you start trekking back to your house!
Hey, tall, dumb, and lazy.
You had to wait until I'd just fallen asleep.
When did Sengoku get here?
And how?
Duh, he walked, ran into him around nine o'clock, brought him over, and then in the middle
of our chat, we both got really sleepy.
Miyamorta, it's midnight already.
Huh?
Oh.
Save it.
Always save before you go in dungeons.
Huh?
Mr. President knows.
Forget it, save's like the worst ever.
Yeah, but before that, buy magic recovery items while you're in town.
Yeah.
A surprise monster encounter, ah!
AHHHHH!
What?
No!
How'd that golem get here?
Was that directed at me?
Calm down!
I'm the quick quirk of the beast with the destruction spell!
How about you calm down?
Yay, we're saved!
The heroes are here!
You stay out of this!
Why?
Is the press here, or am I dreaming?
I was abducted nearby.
Kiyosuke's doing.
I haven't had a bath or eaten dinner.
Just plopped down and passed out.
I still gotta wash up, too.
We have a tub.
Go take your baths together for all I care.
Hori, there's kinda sorta something that he shouldn't see?
What, like a secret birthmark, or...?
Oh, nothing!
Oh, I just remembered that during our school trip!
You waited till late to use the public baths!
I can't seem to recall.
You wouldn't get in the pool, either.
I could never understand why.
Um, well, you see, I'm all skin and bone!
If you're categorized as skin and bone, I'm already dead.
Hey, stop!
That wasn't supposed to be any form of money!
Uh-oh.
Looks like we succumbed yet again.
This kotatsu is dangerous.
Wake up, Miyamura!
Come on, don't leave your phone open.
Text piling up?
I guess I sent those last texts to Miyamura on accident.
Ah, so that's why Chika hasn't shown.
Where are you?
I know it's been cold lately and all, but I'd like to apologize for what happened the other day.
Can you come to the partner's school?
I'll be waiting at our usual spot.
You can say whatever you like, and I promise I'll still love you, even though I don't say it much.
I know you'll understand.
I'll still love you!
Wake up!
I want an explanation!
Shindo, your voice is annoying as ever.
Huh?
Feels like someone smashed their fist into my forehead with every ounce of strength they had.
Nah, must have imagined it.
Ahori?
You asleep?
Oh, just faking?
Well, you might want to stop.
It's eight o'clock.
I'm aware of that.
You're angry, aren't you?
But why?
The world may never know.
I'm not angry!
Really?
Don't make me repeat myself!
Hey, looky here!
We've got some mandarins, your favorite.
I'll peel one for you.
Hm?
Wow.
That actually got her up?
Don't laugh.
Oh, that's right!
I made myself a promise that I would only eat two a day!
So you hate them now?
What gives?
I don't like mandarin-flavored things.
Same with yuzu, citron, and grapefruit.
All the citrus!
I can't even bear to look at it!
Ohori, but it's peeled and ready to go.
Come on.
Get it away!
One slice.
What's the harm?
Eat it!
I'm gonna kiss you if you don't eat it.
I'll also kiss you if you do.
Good.
The storm has passed.
You're not mad anymore.
So that's what he was trying to do.
There was a text that said...
He keeps feeding me things like this.
Is it out of habit?
Want some candy?
Here.
No!
I will not stand for that.
Huh.
It's like clockwork, I swear.
That's from our grade school camping trip.
I didn't expect to find pictures like this here at your place, dude.
Well, we kind of grew up together and all.
You haven't changed a bit.
Except for, like, your height.
Oh, you think so?
That album.
It has pictures we haven't seen?
Give it here.
Oh, it's nothing worth seeing.
Pretty boring, really.
What's in there?
Do you see anything good?
Why don't we play some games, Miyamura?
We've still got no Super Nintendo!
Put the album down and let us go!
12-year-old Sengaku screwed up cutting his hair.
I've got to see that kind of go to my own eyes!
You guys want me to die from there?
Man, this is too funny.
This is a few times, Freddy.
Put the jerks!
You're a lonely con.
No, I am not, I swear!
So, if three's as low as you go,
what's the max age before your interest goes out the window?
I don't go lower than high school,
so let's drop this joke.
Kyochan still changes clothes
in front of other people to this day.
I'm pretty sure zero high school girls
change clothes with an audience.
That includes Hori.
Oh, but she did it fairly recently,
and I was there.
I have gym first period today!
I'm borrowing this room for like five minutes, okay?
Sure, whatever.
I don't have time to go to the locker room.
Kyochan, you're not self-conscious at all, are you?
Even though I haven't moved.
And?
If I'm being honest, I could still use the toilet
or take a bath with you in the same room.
So what?
She thinks so little of it.
He might as well be a fly on the wall.
I found her rationale very strange,
so I asked if she would strip in front of Miyamura, too.
And she said...
No, never in a million years!
Rather aggressively.
Oh, I see.
Sorry, I guess.
I suppose we did take baths together
all the time when we were little kids.
Well, as kids, sure.
Wait, what age did we stop that?
I feel like it dragged on
for an inappropriately long time.
I'm scared to remember.
Kindergarten or so?
Yeah, that sounds right.
Maybe first grade, but not past that.
I can't say it.
Makes sense.
Yeah.
Baron Stock!
Sota said he really likes these,
so I want to give him a try.
I'll go and check out.
Gosh, I am so sorry.
Thank you.
Aren't you Koyanagi?
No, sir.
You're mistaken.
Sengoku?
Wait.
Would you happen to be Hori's daughter?
Yeah!
And you must be Sengoku's father!
Kakaru is always helping.
He's just such a good boy.
Kind of you to say.
So you're the president's father?
It's nice to meet you.
I'm Miyamura.
Your son and I have become
really great friends.
What a difference!
You mustn't be corrupted
by the Hori family, okay?
Huh?
You know, I'm standing within earshot.
His dad seems nice.
I think I'm a fan.
Kakaru's like his clone.
We were looking at the future president
in a way.
But why did he call you Koyanagi?
Oh, that's my mom's maiden name.
My parents went to the same high school
as Sengoku's dad,
so they've known each other
for, like, ever.
Hmm.
I wonder what they were like back then.
Hey, how would you describe
your parents, huh?
My folks?
Hmm.
Normal?
Well, I guess that's one more thing
we have in common, then.
Huh?
How could you drop it
when you would half-laugh, dummy?
You guys, uh...
remain a very few words, huh?
It's not that we're staying quiet.
The conversation just keeps dying.
Help me explain how terrible
he is at this, Kakaru.
I'm not terrible at anything.
I was simply reminiscing
about the good old days.
Ain't that right, right?
Uh, sure.
You can be honest.
In fact, you should be honest.
There you go.
Brushing off someone's opinion
because you don't like...
I hate it here.
It's been cold outside!
Whoa, now there's a face
I didn't expect.
Welcome back!
Is Dad's here, too?
Ah, the pleasant one.
Hurry in and warm up.
Hey!
Why did you two decide to blink me?
You realize there's more room
on the other side?
It's cold over by the window,
so deal.
Now, can you please explain
why you and your dad
are even here?
Your father ran into mine
coming home from work.
I happened to be there, too,
and he abducted us both.
Does getting kidnapped
run on your family, or what?
You're thin enough
that I can feel a giraffe
blowing right through you, Prez.
I apologize.
You live here, too.
Seems like it.
You waltzed in so casually
one could only assume you do.
Well, kind of.
Believe it or not,
he's dating Gyoko.
They're such a cute couple.
Ah.
Well, Kakeru has no time
for dating or silly school drama.
What?
Not that it's wrong, mind you.
My son just doesn't need
a love interest.
It would interfere
with his studies.
So, is he joking with us?
Or have you been lying?
I wouldn't call it
outright lying.
I just haven't gotten around
to telling him the truth.
I thought I'd force an opportunity
by inviting Remy over
on Christmas, but...
I wanted to be in my room!
I wound up going
to her place instead.
I was surrounded by insects.
Yikes.
Though, I've kept quiet
till now.
I do intend to tell him.
Uh...
Are you cold, President?
The way you're shaking
is concerning.
Don't you say a word.
Oh, and what word
would that be?
What's up?
Playing a word game?
Gee, Sengoku.
Just get it off your chest
and tell him
you've been dating for a while.
Will it be the loose cannon?
How's Ayasaki been?
You see her today at school?
Oh, I forgot.
Or the oblivious time bomb.
The time bomb
is the real danger here.
That's you!
But I'm human.
He's a freaking teenager.
Falling in love
is kind of what they do.
Isn't it a little excessive
to say you can't date at all?
This could work.
A peaceful resolution!
Mind your business.
Our family affairs
have nothing to do with you.
Why latch into
those outdated beliefs, Grandpa?
It ain't hip, yo.
We're parents, not hippies.
And did you actually bring me here
in my personal time
to lecture me
when I'm older
and smarter than you are?
You forget who brought you bread
that time you left your lunch.
You mean the bread
that costs 80 yen?
You tricked me
and said it costs 100.
I want my 20 yen!
They completely veered off topic.
It's almost as if...
This isn't an adult conversation.
It's a high school fight.
Don't make me tell him, dude.
Remember when you walked
through what seemed to be
a normal puddle
and got soaked up
to your knees, my friend?
You want the kids to know?
You just told them!
Though remind me,
which moron arrived at school
after all our exams were over?
It only happened
because someone stole
the front wheel of my bike.
You should have
bought the bike and walked!
Good grief.
It's like a bad dream,
but it's real.
Oh, really?
This is par for the course for us.
Wow, I can tell
how close you guys are.
Life-long pals.
Sengoku and I
are the bestest friends.
Ha!
Bestest friends, my ass!
I won't ever forget
what you did to me
on graduation day.
Right as I was giving
my speech
as student council president.
I know that sneeze was planned!
Don't deny it!
And sneeze
was the student body rep.
Our school had no such rep!
Let's circle back
to talking about
Sengoku's love life.
That was fun.
Oh, boy!
I sure wish you'd keep
telling stories
from the good old days!
Don't laugh off
by humiliation!
It seems
even years later,
the Sengokus
are still at the mercy
of the Hodies.
Ha!
But seriously,
a girlfriend
isn't a temptation
you need right now.
Especially if she's
anything like
Hori's daughter.
It got harder
to tell him.
Imports
are like imports
because they come
into Japan.
Hope I can score
at least a 40.
But that might
be pushing it.
I don't know.
Did you do
your math homework yet?
Nope.
I'm dropping it.
I recall you dropping
it at the start
of the term, too.
Try picking math
back up sometimes.
Careful, Hori.
Your nails
will turn orange.
I'm not eating
that, Vinny.
I told you so.
Here.
Sharing it
won't do anything
to save your fingernails,
but okay?
I never thought
it would.
Oh, my gosh.
It's like feeding an animal!
One more!
I cleaned all the orange
job for you.
Huh?
Not what I would call
clean.
Hori, I'm dropping
everything by classic
lead.
Uh, no.
There we go, people are
like franchise, when we offer
new guitar.
Thank you.